Most of us dream of meeting that special someone.
我们大多数人都梦想着遇到那个心仪之人。
For lack of a better phrase, that Prince or Princess charming who will sweep us off our feet.
套用一句再贴切不过的话来说，就是那个能让我们神魂颠倒的白马王子或白雪公主。
But to quote the old adage from Shakespeare, “The course of true love never did run smooth.”
但正如莎士比亚的那句古老格言所言：“真爱之路，从不平坦。”
Sometimes our dream partner may have an unfortunate surprise to share with us – they may not live in the same town, city, country, or even on the same continent as you.
有时候，我们的理想伴侣可能会带来一个令人遗憾的意外——他们或许和我们不在同一个城镇、城市、国家，甚至不在同一个大洲。
And so some crazy lovebirds decide to enter into a long-distance relationship.
于是，有些为爱痴狂的情侣便决定开启一段异地恋。
We live in a time when the internet facilitates easier interaction with your cherished and treasured potential life partner.
如今，互联网的发展让我们能更轻松地与那个心心念念、视若珍宝的潜在人生伴侣互动。
However, according to the many people who have been in long-distance relationships, there are certain pitfalls that you need to be aware of to enjoy a committed and monogamous relationship over the wires of the net.
但许多有过异地恋经历的人表示，若想通过网络维系一段忠诚专一的感情，你需要警惕一些潜在的陷阱。
Many people are put off by the very idea of it.
很多人一听到异地恋这个词就望而却步。
A lack of intimacy and companionship can act as a deterrent for some, but for those who embrace a digital distance relationship, they must accept that at times they may feel lonely.
缺乏亲密感和陪伴感对一些人来说是阻碍，但对于那些选择开启线上异地恋的人而言，他们必须接受自己有时会感到孤独的事实。
Many of us dream of that inseparable bond, often named as ‘soulmates’, and here are three tips to help you navigate this potentially tricky form of dating.
我们很多人都向往一种密不可分的羁绊，也就是人们常说的“灵魂伴侣”关系，以下有三个小建议，能帮你应对这种可能颇具挑战的恋爱模式。
Firstly, there needs to be trust.
首先，彼此之间需要信任。
Being faithful is a prerequisite in most relationships, but you also need to be able to trust yourself not to stray.
忠诚是大多数感情的前提，但你也要相信自己不会变心。
Part of the challenge is dealing with loneliness.
异地恋的挑战之一就是应对孤独感。
Also, maintaining a level of self-sufficiency and setting goals is another way to help you cope.
此外，保持一定的自给自足能力并设定目标，也是帮助你应对这种状态的另一种方式。
Not only does it mean you keep your independence, but also gives you more to talk about with your partner.
这不仅能让你保持独立，还能让你和伴侣有更多话题可聊。
Lastly, you need a plan – dates when you will see each other again, or where the relationship will lead to: perhaps even marriage.
最后，你们需要一个计划——规划好下次见面的时间，或是这段感情的发展方向：甚至可能是步入婚姻殿堂。
So, long-distance relationships are potentially a difficult situation, but if you do meet Mr or Mrs Right, and they live far away, there are some steps you can take to make life a little easier.
所以说，异地恋确实可能是一种颇具挑战的状态，但如果你真的遇到了那个对的人，而对方又住在远方，你可以采取一些措施，让这段感情之路走得更轻松一些。